hey guys it's me Tara and I'm here with
Mr Vinnie hacker yes it's me Vinnie was
supposed to be on my channel 3 months
ago and then he wasn't we not well that
wasn't my fault that's okay I just he
said yes I'm so down and then it just
went crickets not my fault crickets not
my fault run into a problem I have a
problem what's your problem I don't like
the side of my face so could we switch
positions yeah okay really yeah okay am
I allowed to move your seat yeah you can
also move the booster oh my God no way
oh my [ __ ] god what it's a booster I
don't want to be a problem to people on
the road Jesus this is a new series I'm
doing on my channel called stuck in a
car with blank and today we're stuck in
a car with Vinnie hacker this is so fun
already I'm so excited I don't like your
sarcastic tone it's not sarcasm it's
just the way I speak I wouldn't know cuz
we were supposed to film 3 months ago
and then we didn't so I apologize I
apologize for that something about
Vinnie and I is every time I've met
Vinnie it's been Halloween and I've been
in ridiculous costumes I've met him as
Patrick baitman which he doesn't
remember but that's okay I'm not hurt um
your costumes are just too good oh my
god really mhm thank you and then the
first time we like introduced ourselves
I was dressed like Justin [ __ ] Bieber
like of course so good cuz how else
would you meet me it was right after I
sang One Less Lonely Girl to our mutual
friend for her birthday mhm and I walked
off my little stage and the first person
stage for little people the first person
I ran into was you and you're like that
was really good ni cuz it was gas I
think so too but I think most people
would find it I don't know humiliating
anyway then the third time we met I was
dressed like Coraline I'm always in a
wig I don't ever look like myself so
this is the first time we're actually
seeing each other and I'm Tara and not
justtin very nice to meet you in a
different you know in your
actual hello I think it's trying to say
something about us it's oh it's a recy
yeah it's recycling what if I just picks
up my car and recycles us what would you
do probably die that's kind of
romantic my first thing I I noticed
about you is that your appearance
doesn't really like match what I read
online about you you know what I mean
what did you read online about me
hindered that I wrote anime uhhuh
editing yeah I do that Star Wars yeah I
love Star Wars and video games I love
that too no question and this is like a
no offense thing does that like does
that seem like kind of nerdy to you I
mean yeah but I really you know it's
whatever I mean a lot of the time the
reason why I hate like going on planes
and stuff and like being away from my
house is because I'd much rather be
sitting there playing video games after
the time or you know like editing things
not going to say what things but I'm
editing yeah and like this is no offense
to like nerdy Behavior like to each
their own like whatever but do you find
that kind of nerdy yeah and do you think
you look nerdy depends cuz I don't it
depends if I'm in if I'm in my element
if I'm sitting down at a chair hunched
over like that no I think someone could
like literally make you the nerd's
personal alive and you still wouldn't
look nerdy like well maybe not with the
tattoos now not even the tattoos I just
feel like just like you're just like
like the world thinks you're hot you
know what I mean so it's like I was
waiting for that one oh boohoo I'm hot
like God who said boohoo I didn't say
booh I was waiting for that one as if
it's like some kind of Burden hear come
out of your mouth way better that way I
just think it doesn't match it doesn't
add up also these are all things that I
have no I I know nothing about I know
nothing about anime I've watched three
episodes of one anime and it's death not
I don't know anything about anime I
don't how did you not finish that that's
such a good show cuz I don't like
cartoons I'm sorry I know I I'm ignorant
Vinnie you uploaded like a year ago on
YouTube M why like why have I not
uploaded yeah why haven't you uploaded
are you just like a streamer now I mean
I haven't even been streaming a lot
recently I've been so packed with like
whenever I travel my like not my sleep
schedule but just like my sleep in
general I don't get like any sleep for
like 2 weeks straight so I'm always
trying to like I'm like okay I'm going
to take this like time to relax when I
get back by the time I'm relaxed I leave
again for work and can you define work
modeling modeling ladies and gentlemen
did you know that when I was 18 I tried
to go like I tried to like you know
pursue modeling and then they laughed in
my face well if it makes you feel any
better I got denied by like three
agencies cuz I was only like 5'11 it's
weird because when I saw you I'm like oh
you're taller than I remember in my head
you're like 5'
seven I knew that would get you so
that's why I know did you know anything
about me I knew who you were for the
longest time I already told you that a
while ago it's for the camera okay yeah
yeah we had a we had a little discussion
over text little back and forth yelling
at each other I was yelling at you for
[ __ ] not filming with me for did you
know I bought you a Christmas swe did
you know that why would you buy me a
because I wanted to film a Christmas
video with you and it was really cute
and I was like oh cool he said he's very
down to take it
I actually have it I didn't bring it but
I have it have okay well the sweater
says wrapping presence is hard but I'm
harder oh that's G and there's like a
little bow on the dang it I know it was
really good
Jinx now I can't talk I don't know
what's the rules in Jinx you want me a
soda what kind of soda do you like are
you a big soda drinker no do you like
soda at all not really okay so I just
want one it's part of the game okay my
bad I just feel like I don't know the
rules of jinx I know there's one Jinx
rule where it's like you can't talk
until someone says your name three times
no what I don't know maybe my friends
are bullies I just wanted me to shut the
[ __ ] up I have never heard that yeah
maybe honestly this all makes sense
maybe they just wanted me to shut the
[ __ ] up and that's why they said you
can't talk until someone says your name
three times video Interruption sorry I
just want to take a second to thank my
video sponsor for this video better help
I personally am in therapy and I
absolutely adore therapy with better
help starting therapy is a lot less
intimidating and it's a lot easier on a
lot of people it's whatever is easiest
for you whether that's video chatting
messaging phone calls with better help
they can match you to one to 30,000
therapists based on your needs and
preferences you just take a
questionnaire and in most cases it takes
less than 48 hours to match you to a
therapist you can schedule therapy
sessions that are convenient for you the
great thing is is if you don't feel like
you and your therapist Vibe or a good
match you can break up with your
therapist by a click of a button and
just switch one join over 4 million
people that use better help to live a
happier and healthier life with my link
betterhelp.com Tar yumy this link will
help you get 10% off your first month
using betterhelp I love therapy so much
so I just want to give a huge thanks to
better help for sponsoring this video my
favorite thing to talk about with people
is their celebrity crush cuz I feel like
growing up I was like obsessed with
celebrities and like having a celebrity
crush and like
mhm you have to think about it for that
long like if someone's like who's your
celebrity crush you can't think of it
off the top of your head yeah I don't
know did you have a celebrity crush when
you were a kid wait can I phone a friend
sure you get one phone call my mom will
know oh okay good 5 minutes later your
celebrity crush growing up yeah was
there anybody um I'm thinking of your um
like your dream board you made remember
I said that to you oh God you had like
all this stuff but actually pretty a lot
of it came true and that you were going
to meet Paris that you were G to want to
meet Paris
Hilton she's my idol that's
awesome oh God did you know that it's my
dream to meet Paris hon she's my idol
mhm she's great I say it all the time
she follows me on Tik Tok but I'm like I
say it all the time in every video I do
probably that she's my idol and I think
the day I meet par you should get her on
you should get her on for a YouTube
video I don't think she'd everever want
to why would she ever want to
presentence me with her grace she would
love that oh my God I think I would
literally throw up all over her if I met
her is that a good thing or a bad thing
a good thing I'd just be so I don't know
depends on what you're into yeah I don't
know if paran's in a throw up though I
don't think she's into Von play no no
what about did you ever get compared to
a celebrity growing up I got compared to
asht and Kutcher when I uh whenever I
put a hat on oh really I get compared to
munas all the time look at that yeah
they're married now that could be us one
day you want to get married to me yep do
it tomorrow I Don't Think You'd Survive
a day a day even just being with like
being with me there's no Hur and trying
you just get a divorce you know if it
doesn't work out you have a divorce by
her name yeah why not but there's some
benefits that can come with it that's
true there are what like taxes taxes
taxes Let's Get Married let's get
married so we could and we can do taxes
together you would hate doing I actually
have a tax like a tax thing with my guy
tomorrow he hates me like my tax guy was
like you need to stop shopping for
clothes you have a shopping I had a
problem with spending money on video
games for a while mini hacker everyone
buying CSO cases what I can't gauge what
kind of music you like if you were to
guess what would you say I don't know I
wouldn't I wouldn't look at you and
guess you like anime or you like Star
Wars so I can't look at you and guess
the music like if you were to take a
wild guess a wild guess based on what
based on stuff I already know about you
or based on just what you look like yeah
just what you know about me I don't know
it's hard watch what do you think I
listen to wait I feel like that's easy
um listen to
pop no mm- Rock classic rock yeah yeah
classic Rock's good mhm I like jazz you
like jazz I love jazz I just feel like
everyone in their mothers are like oh my
God Vinnie ha you're so hot like have my
babies no okay so most of the time
actually when people like meet me like
for the first time or something or like
see me they like don't appro I've had
like friends who are my friends now like
they said when they first were like
approaching me or whatever they didn't
want to because I looked like just like
pissed off I didn't want to talk talk to
anybody like let's say I'm like at a
house party and I like know like the
person that's hosting it but nobody else
sit in well no I knew I knew a decent
amount of oh did you yeah why are you
smiling why are you laughing about that
because I've only ever seen you out on
Halloween like I've never seen you out
you don't go out yeah no that's true
like I've only ever seen you on
Halloween parties ever Anakin yeah dude
every year he dresses up as Anakin he I
dressed up as Ki ones you don't know who
that is though because you're stupid I
don't know who that is got me there I
don't know [ __ ] about Star Wars I'm
sorry I'm not a Star Wars It's anime oh
see exactly my point exactly you know
what I like I like shopping I like shoes
I like
vibrators what yeah I heard that story
what story I'm kidding was a joke I'm
like what what have you heard about me
see this what I mean it's like you know
like I've heard a lot about you what
have you heard about me you know people
talk I heard you throw great parties I
do throw great parties I did actually
hear that from somebody really mhm oh my
God you don't know what that does for me
I don't but I'm I can can kind of tell
yeah yeah I love throwing good parties
and the fact that you're not going to be
here for my one M party I know I'm sad
I'm sad I invited you to my birthday
last year that no I think I would I
think I would have remembered would have
remembered I think you would have
remembered actually because don't go out
you probably wouldn't know because
people get really drunk at my
parties good point yeah people get
really drunk at mine too thanks for
inviting
me I invited you to
mine you want to be invited this year
yeah yeah were you popular in high
school no really I was really quiet I
didn't go out I didn't do anything but
play video games or watch anime I
actually went back to a bar one time oh
people were probably like oh my God and
I saw these two girls I knew from holy
names which I didn't mind them you know
like I never thought that they were
weird or anything but they came up to me
and they were like hey V I was like oh
hey guys and they were like yeah we got
into a conversation that ended up
leading into her like one of them being
like yeah I just remember in high school
everybody thought you were [ __ ] weird
cuz you just didn't talk I was
like that's so how does that how does
that equivalate not talking to being
weird I mean I guess it could but no I
don't think so I also like I feel like I
talked to everyone in high school and
like even people who were quiet I like
tried to get them to talk and like talk
to me I never thought people were weird
just cuz they were quiet I think being
weird is cool being weird is so dope
what's your favorite movie star wars
yeah mine's being girls got to guess
that yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what else
do I have on here oh the last thing is
Vin vent question mark I wanted to know
if your full name is Vincent yeah
Vincent Cole hacker okay the camera
overheated everyone Vinnie's just too
hot that's a bar that was good right
that's a bar yeah um or at least
everyone thinks he is are you ever
scared of like being a catfish or do you
think you know your hot in person I
think I know that I'm attractive in
person there he is every there he is
we're so dark it's going to [ __ ]
drive me
nuts should we drive around yeah do you
want to I trust you all right well I'm
going to have to scoot back a little bit
yeah that's fine oh my God you know
where we're going where we're going to a
studio a studio yeah what do you what do
you what kind of what do you mean it has
a couch on it wait what are you talking
about what do you mean Studio can you
define Studio what are you saying did
you really not get that everybody's
going to get
that that was kind of outlandish though
oh my God I just got it what's your
favorite song Maneater ooh I love that
song look at me
a few moments later do you like my car I
know you like cars yes I love this car
actually really fits you very well thank
you but I mean like just in general do
you like it I mean personally yes so
much good answer I'd be pissed what's
your favorite tattoo you have one of my
you don't have one on your wiener I have
a wiener on my wiener no you don't yeah
I have a wiener on my wiener I don't
believe
you no actually though oh you don't
believe me just whips it out you don't
believe me we're in a neighborhood
there's children around
Vinnie get us out of here people have
been complaining about my video is being
really short so I hope this one's long
enough for you
[Music]
um what's your favorite show like just
regular show mhm Regular Show what like
what's your favorite show Regular Show
yeah like a Regular Show Regular
Show is that a show name yes oh it's
about bird and a raccoon and a gumball
oh I know that show yeah Regular Show
you know for being called The Regular
Show it's very weird it's about a bird
and a raccoon and oh
really think about it I did thanks what
do you think this is Vinnie hacker
making t feel stupid for however long
this video is supposed to be you're so
smart I told you I'm very smart and
funny and humble and sexy and pretty and
cute and fun all the above all the above
I'm the full package indeed indeed you
are guys make sure you like this video
if you like video on my channel um
comment down below who or what you guys
want to see next thank you for coming of
course
anytime that's what she said it's time
to
SC
take